那潮水，擺蕩目前
The tide sways against our gaze
在這晚風的和煦之間
in the grace of the midnight winds
那光芒，如此輝煌
The brilliance of light
在這空中，我們指引
between the skies, our guides in flight
在我們這受護的使命中
And between our Sheltered Destinies
我們能夠重連之前
we can bridge the days again
而在這地照的場景之下
And a spectacle of earthshine
我們的心也終平靜
do our hearts create a peace
在我們這受護的使命底
And beneath our Sheltered Destinies
一種魅力竄出
a fascination grows
月亮跟太陽合一
The moon and the sun as one
一個生命的徵兆
a symbol of life itself
在我們這受護的使命中
And between our Sheltered Destinies
我們能夠重連之前
we can bridge the days again
而在這地照的場景之下
And a spectacle of earthshine
我們的心也終平靜
do our hearts create a peace
在我們這受護的使命底
And beneath our Sheltered Destinies
一種魅力竄出
a fascination grows
月亮跟太陽合一
The moon and the sun as one
一個生命的徵兆
a symbol of life itself
在我們這受護的使命底
And beneath our Sheltered Destinies
一種魅力竄出
a fascination grows
月亮跟太陽合一
The moon and the sun as one
一個生命的徵兆
a symbol of life itself
噢，真是一場約定
Oh and it's a promise
由星群簽署
between the stars
你是否能夠聽見
Can you hear my voice
離我如此多里遠？
all these miles away?